Carl W. Schaefer Papers 2001.0016
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
Carl W. Schaefer Papers
undated, 1963-1992.
2001.0016
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
20.8 Linear feet
Dr. Carl W. Schaefer is a professor in the Ecology and Evolutionary Biology Department at the University of Connecticut. The collection documents his professional interests and activities.
Schaefer, Carl W. (Carl Walter)
Biography
Information concerning Dr. Carl W. Schaefer and his professional interests and activities is available on the Ecology and Evolutionary Biology Department website.
Scope and Content
The collection contains materials pertaining to Dr. Schaefer's professional activities as the editor of several publications as well as his research interests.
Arrangement
Series I: Inventory ( undated, 1963-1992 )
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University, its history, administration, faculty, staff and students. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
Dr. Schaefer donated his papers in several installments beginning in 2001.
Schaefer, Carl W.; University of Connecticut--Faculty.; Administrative Records.; Biology--Study and teaching.; College teachers--Connecticut.; Correspondence.; Ecology--Study and teaching.; Financial Records.; Manuscripts.; Minutes.; Molecular biology--Study and teaching.; Notebooks.; Notes.; Photocopies.; Publications.
- Series I: Inventory, undated, 1963-1992
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 1)
  - Materials pertaining to editorialship of Annals of the Entomological Society of America, undated, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - Annals of the Entomological Society of America related documents and correspondence, undated, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Annals of the Entomological Society of America related documents and correspondence, undated (Box 3)
  - Annals of the Entomological Society of America related documents and correspondence, undated, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Masters Thesis by John Kuchle, undated (Box 5)
  - Biological Science Series materials, undated (Box 5)
  - Humanistic Studies Series, undated (Box 5)
  - Monograph Series, undated (Box 5)
  - University of Connecticut Public Series, undated (Box 5)
  - University of Connecticut Publications, undated (Box 5)
  - Fiancial records, undated (Box 5)
  - Occasional Papers, undated (Box 5)
  - Occasional Papers--proofs, designs, management records, undated (Box 5)
  - Occasional Papers-Biological Science Series, undated (Box 5)
  - Charts, undated (Box 5)
  - Subscriptions Correspondence, undated (Box 5)
  - Occasional Papers-Biological Science Series--manuscripts, undated (Box 5)
  - Entomological Society of America, undated, 1963 (Box 6)
  - Kennedy Commission, undated (Box 6)
  - Publications Council materials, undated, 1985-1996 (Box 6)
  - Tauber Publications Committee, undated, 1990-1992 (Box 6)
  - North American Immigrant Anthropod Database, undated (Box 6)
  - Journal on Biological Control, undated (Box 6)
  - Electronic Publishing, undated (Box 6)
  - Annals of the Entomological Society of America materials, undated (Box 6)
  - Skip Nault Publication Ideas, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Mosquito Genera Abbreviations, undated (Box 6)
  - Annals of the Entomological Society of America documents and correspondence, undated (Box 7)
  - Occasional Papers materials, undated (Box 7)
  - University Senate minutes, undated (Box 7)
  - Biological Science Series manuscripts, undated (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 8)
  - Publication records, undated (Box 8)
  - Governing Board minutes, undated (Box 8)
  - Unpublished (?) Schaefer Paper on Insect Sex Pheromones, undated (Box 8)
  - Paper by Sherill Cyr, "Cycle of Mayfly,", undated (Box 8)
  - Schaefer Manuscripts and Articles, undated (Box 9-14)
  - Chapter 1 of Schaefer's Economic Importance of Heteroptera, undated (Box 15)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 15)
  - CRC Press Contract, undated (Box 15)
  - Research Foundation grant, undated (Box 15)
  - Marketing, undated (Box 15)
  - Indexes, undated (Box 15)
  - Permission Forms, undated (Box 15)
  - Description of Book/Chapters, undated (Box 15)
  - 9-Pentatomidae, undated (Box 15)
  - 7-Lygaeidae, undated (Box 15)
  - Gerridae, undated (Box 15)
  - 16-Belostomatidae, undated (Box 15)
  - 14-Anthocoridae, undated (Box 15)
  - 2-Phytophagous Feeding-Hori, undated (Box 15)
  - 27-Adventitious Biting, undated (Box 15)
  - 10-Pyrrhocoridae, undated (Box 15)
  - 13-Carnivorous Groups-Al Cohen, undated (Box 15)
  - Small Pentatomoid Families, undated (Box 16)
  - 18-Miridae (Predaceous), undated (Box 16)
  - 8-Miridae, undated (Box 16)
  - 12-Tingidae, undated (Box 16)
  - 1-Overview: Introduction Chapter 1, undated (Box 16)
  - Table of Contents and Chapter Sequence, undated (Box 16)
  - 11-Scutelleridae, undated (Box 16)
  - 17-Lygaeidae: Geocorinae, undated (Box 16)
  - 6-Cydnidae, undated (Box 16)
  - 31?-Berytudae, undated (Box 16)
  - 4-Aradidae, undated (Box 16)
  - 26-Triatominae, undated (Box 16)
  - 20-Naucoridae, undated (Box 16)
  - 19-Nabidae, undated (Box 16)
  - 23-Reduviidae, undated (Box 16)
  - 3-Acydidae, undated (Box 16)
  - 5-Coreidae, undated (Box 16)
  - 21-Predaceous Aquatic Bugs Nepomorpha (Papacek), undated (Box 16)
  - 24-Thausmatocoridae, undated (Box 16)
  - 22-Piesmatidae, undated (Box 16)
  - Nepidae-10?, undated (Box 16)
  - 25-Cimicidae, undated (Box 16)
  - Rhopalidae-9?, undated (Box 16)
  - 15-Asopinae, undated (Box 16)